why you'd be a good person to hire.
When it comes to resumes, there is no one standard formatter template to use, though there
are many templates available online if you need help starting out.
Most resumes do, however, contain certain standard sections and information.
It's always good to include a cover letter along with your resume.
If you think of a resume as a summary of information and facts about yourself, a cover letter is
an opportunity to expand on that information, as well as create a personalized message about
why you want the job, why you're interested in the company, and most importantly, why you
would be the best person to hire.
As a rule of thumb, try to keep your resume to two pages or less in your cover letter to
no longer than one page.
Here are a few general tips for preparing a resume and cover letter.
Think spelling and grammar carefully.
With so much competition for jobs, spelling and grammatical errors are an easy way for
those hiring to eliminate applicants since it shows a lack of attention to detail.
Your objective with your resume should be to sell yourself.
Use it to show your strengths, skills, accomplishments, and abilities.
You want your resume to make you stand out from others.